dalidecals.com 2015-08-11

# Privacy Policy

At Dali Decals, your privacy is our priority. We are committed to protecting your privacy at all times, in all situations. The information we collect about you when you become a customer is used to process your orders and to provide a more personalized experience on our site. However, Dali Custom Decals does not guarantee complete security of stored information.

How Do We Use the Information We Collect?  
When you become a Dali Decals customer, we ask you to fill out a form that requests your name, address and e-mail address as well as some demographic information. Dali Decals will not share data.  

Your demographic information will be used for several security purposes, to ensure you are who you say you are and in fact you are paying with your credit cards and not someone using your stolen credit cards.

Refer-A-Friend  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Dali Decals does not store this information and uses it for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

Our Use of Log Files  
When you visit our site we automatically log your IP address, your browser type and your access times. We utilize this information to conduct site performance evaluations, to see where visitors are coming from and to keep track of click stream data (the screens our users visit on our site). This data helps us to determine what content our members find most appealing so that we can maximize your enjoyment of the site. Log files are not tied to personally identifiable information.

Site Security  
All Dali Decals employees take your personal information very seriously. All employees must learn and obey our security policies. Access to member personal information is limited to key management personnel and our member services department. The information is ID and password protected and our Web security is reviewed on a regular basis.

Correcting/Updating Your Personal Information  
After becoming a Dali Decals customer you may correct/update your personal information by clicking on the 'Modify Profile' link under the 'Your Cart' section on the left side of any page. The changes you make will be reflected in our databases instantly. If you wish to deactivate your account, you may contact our member services group through the 'Contact Us' section.

Links To Other Sites  
This Web site may contain links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you may be leaving the Dali Decals site and entering another web site. These sites may independently collect or request information about you and we encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policy may differ from ours.

Communication  
From time to time we may send out email messages alerting you that products are available, to remind you about providing feedback, or to inform you of promotional offers. In addition, you will receive communications from us 1) if you contact us for a particular reason, 2) to receive your orders, or 3) we need to contact you for administrative purposes such as winning a contest. Administrative e-mails will not contain promotional materials.

Legal Disclaimer  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site

Supplementation  
We may correct or supplement your address information with standardized postal representation in order to ensure that your orders are delivered. We do this since we want to make sure that our customers receive the order and to lower costs associated with our programs.

Contests  
Periodically, contests are run on our site. To enter these contests, you must be a member of **Dali Decals**.

Our Use of Cookies  
Cookies are pieces of information that your browser stores on your computer's hard drive which identify you when you enter. The ability to select samples on our site is not cookie-driven. We may use session cookies to provide a seamless experience on the site and to combine with our log files so that we can understand our site traffic and analyze our demographic information in aggregate form. If you have set your browser to reject cookies, our site will not identify you when you enter and you will need to manually type in your ID and password.

Your Feedback is Always Welcome  
We welcome your comments and questions about our privacy policy - or anything else you might want to talk about.
